Previously on the show.
Episode sebelumnya.
Hope used her remote control wings to deliver the weather fruits,
Hope pakai sayap kendalinya untuk mengirim buah cuaca,
but blew up the canteen by accident.
tapi meledakkan kantin tanpa sengaja.
Paddi's words inspired Hope to upgrade her wings,
Kata-kata Paddi mengilhami Hope untuk memperbagus sayap,
and resolved the delivery problem of the weather fruits.
dan mengatasi masalah pengiriman buah cuaca.
Can Weslie and Paddi finally leave?
Bisakah Weslie dan Paddi akhirnya pergi?
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: Weather Seeds."
Petualangan Langit Pulau Terbang: Benih Cuaca.
Announcement. New order arrived for 500 weather fruits.
Pengumuman. Ada pesanan baru 500 buah cuaca.
Complete.
Selesai.
It took only ten seconds to complete 500 fruits.
Hanya butuh sepuluh detik untuk kirim 500 buah.
Thank you for helping us with the delivery problem.
Terima kasih sudah bantu atasi masalah pengiriman.
Since the delivery problem is solved,
Karena masalah pengiriman sudah selesai, kita bisa cari kepala desa yang lain.
Where do you think you're going?
Kau mau ke mana?
All you think about is collecting spare parts to repair Sirius,
Kau terus cari suku cadang untuk perbaiki Sirius,
but you never catch a goat.
tapi tak pernah menangkap kambing.
You can't go!
Kau tak boleh pergi!
Okay.
Baiklah.
"Where do you think you are going? You never catch a goat.
"Kau mau ke mana? Kau tak pernah menangkap kambing.
You can't go!"
Kau tak boleh pergi!"
Thank you, Hope. You don't have to see us off.
Terima kasih, Hope. Kau tak perlu mengantar kami.
I hope you can find your friends soon.
Semoga bisa segera bertemu temanmu.
Did something explode?
Ada yang meledak?
Maybe the thunder fruit exploded again.
Mungkin buah petir meledak lagi.
It happens all the time. Don't be scared.
Itu sering terjadi. Jangan takut.
Why are you making that face?
Kenapa wajahmu begitu?
The weather tree has been hit by a cannon!
Pohon cuaca ditembak oleh meriam!
Oh, no!
Tidak!
Let's go and help them.
Ayo kita bantu.
Catch the fruits. Watch out, everyone!
Tangkap buahnya. Awas, Semuanya!
Oh, no!
Tidak!
The fruits on the weather tree withered.
Buah di pohon cuaca layu.
What should we do now?
Kita harus bagaimana?
The weather tree must be repaired immediately.
Pohon cuaca harus diperbaiki.
Yes, but what about the coming order?
Ya, tapi bagaimana urutannya?
Without the weather tree, we can't produce weather fruits.
Tanpa pohon cuaca, kita tak bisa menghasilkan buah cuaca.
Right, we have weather seeds.
Tunggu, kita punya benih cuaca.
Weather seeds?
Benih cuaca?
It'll be fine
Tak apa-apa jika kita tanam pohon cuaca baru sebelum stok habis.
Weather trees grow very quickly.
Pohon cuaca tumbuh sangat cepat.
These weather seeds are glowing.
Benih cuaca ini bersinar.
Watch out! Catch that wind fruit.
Awas! Tangkap buah angin itu.
The seeds!
Benihnya.
Look carefully. We must find the seeds.
Cari secara teliti. Kita harus dapat benihnya.
They're over there.
Ada di sana.
The seed.
Benihnya.
The seed?
Benihnya?
Where is it?
Di mana?
I'm sorry.
Maaf.
It's all right. We'll keep searching.
Tak apa-apa. Kami akan terus cari.
Look!
Lihat!
The seed.
Benihnya.
What should we do?
Kita harus bagaimana?
Don't worry. We'll find the rest.
Tenang. Kita akan temukan sisanya.
Let's look over there.
Coba kita cari di sana.
Okay.
Baiklah.
What's wrong?
Ada apa?
Wolffy is here.
Wolffy ada di sini.
How come I don't see any goats today?
Kenapa aku tak melihat kambing hari ini?
The seed!
Benihnya!
Seeds? Where?
Benih? Di mana?
-I see goats. -Oh, no!
- Ada kambing. - Tidak!
I'll get you.
Kutangkap kalian!
Wolffy, give us back the seed.
Wolffy, kembalikan benihnya.
-Paddi, hurry! Let's help them! -Okay.
- Paddi, cepat! Kita bantu mereka. - Baik.
Little goats, it's your turn.
Kambing kecil, kini giliranmu.
We must get the seed on Wolffy's head back.
Kita harus ambil benih di kepala Wolffy.
If only we can fly above Wolffy.
Andai kita bisa terbang di atas Wolffy.
Fly?
Terbang?
I have an idea.
Aku punya ide.
Paddi, action.
Paddi, ,mulai.
This is strange. Where did the goats go?
Ini aneh. Ke mana para kambing tadi?
Isn't that Paddi's Hurricane?
Bukankah itu Hurikan milik Paddi?
Paddi!
Paddi!
Weslie.
Weslie.
Weslie, run. Don't worry about me.
Weslie, lari. Jangan cemaskan aku.
No, Paddi. I won't leave you.
Tidak, Paddi. Aku takkan meninggalkanmu.
Where's Paddi's Hurricane? Did I let him get away?
Di mana Hurikan Paddi? Apa sudah kulepaskan?
But I have Weslie. It'll work, too.
Tak apa-apa, toh aku punya Weslie.
I've collected the mark energy.
Aku sudah mengumpulkan energi tanda.
This goat is going to be my food!
Kambing ini akan segera kusantap.
I'm the winner wolf!
Aku serigala pemenangnya!
It's you again, Paddi?
Ini kau lagi, Paddi?
You guys are ganging up on me.
Kalian mengeroyokku.
Fight me one on one if you're strong enough. Ouch!
Lawan aku satu lawan satu jika kau cukup kuat. Aduh!
Weslie, get in!
Weslie, masuk!
Mr. Wolffy, thank you.
Pak Wolffy, terima kasih.
Get back here!
Kembali kemari!
This is great. We got the seed back.
Bagus. Kita dapat benihnya kembali.
Great!
Bagus!
Paddi, both your hands are here. Who is flying it then?
Paddi, kedua tanganmu di sini. Lalu siapa yang menerbangkannya?
Thank goodness.
Syukurlah.
Paddi, are you all right?
Paddi, kau baik-baik saja?
I... I'm fine. The seed...
Aku tak apa-apa, tapi benihnya...
What's wrong with the seed?
Benihnya kenapa?
Is it still with you? Thank goodness.
Masih kau pegang? Syukurlah.
I... I swallowed it by accident.
Aku tak sengaja menelannya!
What?
Apa?
TO BE CONTINUED 2779 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
BERSAMBUNG 2.779 HARI SEBELUM PULANG